<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writings. on Tin Skoric</title>
    <link>https://tins.page/works/writings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writings. on Tin Skoric</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tins.page/works/writings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Short Look at Rural Education</title>
      <link>https://tins.page/works/writings/ruraleducation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tins.page/works/writings/ruraleducation/</guid>
      <description>A Short Look at Rural EducationTin Skoric December 13, 2022
A Bit About Small TownsThere is a saying, oft-repeated in the description of plaguing ills, which tells very well the tragedy of places that are neither wholly rural, nor truly city and are certainly not suburbia. First slowly, then suddenly. The small town—the rural city—is a pocket—a vestige of what could have been looking out from some time immemorial when suburbia had not yet come to dominate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rural Infrastructure and The Food Deserts of Vermont</title>
      <link>https://tins.page/works/writings/vermontfooddeserts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tins.page/works/writings/vermontfooddeserts/</guid>
      <description>Rural Infrastructure and The Food Deserts of VermontTin Skoric August 20, 2022
Tragic AmericanaAverage Poverty Rate by County (VT) Source: USDA ERS (2019)Download
There is a certain aesthetic present in contemporary critiques of rural American life. That of the sugary drink guzzling, Big Mac obliterating, personification of health complications working some kind of manual job in some kind of dying industry. The thing is that it does not come from nowhere, many people eat and live lives just like that, but what is one to do when their closest affordable meal for miles, painfully, is from a fast-food chain?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vibes-Based Economics</title>
      <link>https://tins.page/works/writings/vibesbasedeconomics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tins.page/works/writings/vibesbasedeconomics/</guid>
      <description>Vibes-Based EconomicsTin Skoric July 31, 2022
Something Isn’t RightThere has been a lot in the news about “recession” recently and, considering current data, it does not make much sense. While wages went up (USBLS) and comparatively decent jobs remain available, half the country seems to think that we are back in 2008. Hell, unemployment is back to pre-pandemic levels (USBLS), with long-term unemployment (27 weeks or more) falling as well, and the federal funds rate, while rising steeply, just hit what it was around this same time in 2019 (FRED).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Racial Disparities Among Unhoused Communities</title>
      <link>https://tins.page/works/writings/racialdisparitiesamongunhousedcommunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tins.page/works/writings/racialdisparitiesamongunhousedcommunities/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Racial Disparities Among Unhoused CommunitiesTin Skoric December 1, 2021
PrefaceMany of the data visualizations used are stylized with some having elements, including axis labels, removed for the sake of simplicity. When viewing data visualizations, keep in mind the direction of data more than what individual numeric values may be. As a final note, it could be possible that the realities of those experiencing houselessness over the past decade have been entirely different from what are identified as national trends, and were just masked under family houselessness, which is sometimes difficult to track accurately, especially given the limitations of the PIT count system, which only records individuals that can be found on the street one night a year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
